目 前 资 金
最 新 余 额
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
打工
姐妹花
第十集
第三季
打工
姐妹花
第十集
第三季
翻校  泡面大厨赛太公
翻校  泡糊小厨YY猫
后期 泡泡亲爱的灰灰
时间轴 总监  泡糊小厨YY猫
麦克斯  我知道新时间表该怎么排了
Okay, Max, I figured out our new schedule.
我也才知道我们用的便宜牙膏
And I figured out the cheap toothpaste
其实是放尿布疹软膏
we've been using is really diaper cream.
但好歹我牙龈上的尿布疹都消了
On the plus side, that rash cleared up on my gums.
晚上6点到清晨2点在餐厅上班
We'll do our diner shift from 6:00 till 2:00,
清晨2点到清晨4点卖小蛋糕
then sell cupcakes here from 2:00 to 4:00,
早上7点到11点做小蛋糕
make the cupcakes in the morning from 7:00 to 11:00,
然后中午12点到下午4点去学校
And then pastry school from 12:00 to 4:00.
-有忘了什么吗  -拉屎跟睡觉时间
- Forget anything? - Just poopin' and sleepin'.
现在我得去重安排时间表了
Now, I have to go rewrite the schedule.
来吧  麦克斯  明天是你的超超大日子
Let's go, Max, you have a huge, huge day tomorrow.
第一天上烘焙学校
First day of pastry school.
别说"超超大"了
Stop saying it's huge.
每次以为要看到"超大东西"时
Whenever I think something's gonna be huge,
最后都只看到"大巨蛋"
It just turns out to be all balls.
我花钱干洗了我的衬衫
I splurged and had my blouse cleaned.
这干洗袋让我想起了当有钱人的时光
Dry cleaning bags remind me of when I had money.
那袋子只让我回想起
Really? They remind me of
我妈曾想把我闷死
when my mother tried to suffocate me.
据说而已啦  走吧
Allegedly. Let's go.
等等  麦克斯  你还不能走
Wait, wait. Max, you can't go yet.
我需要你留下来帮忙一件事
I need you to stay and help with something.
阿憨  我都教过你了
Han, I told you-- it's bend and wipe,
弯下身擦屁股  裤子拉上穿穿好
then up come your big boy pants.
阿憨说得对  你不能走
Yeah, Han's right. You can't go.
再待一会吧
Stay here a few more minutes.
为啥
Why?
我们要开麦克斯的批斗大会吗
Are we having an intervention for Max?
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我还没错过"欢庆麦克斯
Oh, I hope I'm not late for Max's
首日上学惊喜派对"吧
first day of school surprise party.
苏菲  我们都还没给她惊喜呢
Sophie, we hadn't surprised her yet.
她站在这都听见啦
Oh, but she's right there.
惊喜都被你剧透光了  阿憨
You just blew it, Han.
有惊喜派对呢
Aw, a surprise party.
-是不是很温馨啊  麦克斯  -我才不信咧
- Isn't this sweet, Max? - I don't trust it.
上次奥列格给过我"惊喜"
Last time Oleg yelled "surprise" at me,
他把鸡鸡塞在热狗面包中间了
his penis was on a hot dog bun.
一盒肉香满溢披萨
One meat lover's pizza.
一位肉欲满溢爱人
And one meat lover.
麦克斯  快来  "趁热享用"哦
Max, come on. Get it while it's hot.
你去打开那盒子
You're opening that box.
谁有十块钱
Hm, who's got a ten
给这个可爱的送披萨男小费啊
to tip the cute pizza delivery guy?
苏菲  他是路易斯  白班服务生
Sophie, this is Luis, the day waiter.
你就是苏菲啊
Oh, you're Sophie,
奥列格的前任
Oleg's ex.
姐妹  我对你了如指掌
Sister, I know all about you.
真的咩
Oh, do you?
你真的对我从里到外都了解吗
Do you know all about me?
我是他的好朋友
I'm his good friend.
你的口音有点重  我听不太清楚
You know, I'm having trouble hearing your accent.
是"好朋友"还是"女"朋友啊
Did you say "good friend" or "girlfriend?"
拜托  我倒想呢
Please, mami. I wish.
我喜欢这娱乐节目啊
I like the entertainment.
比我朋友妮妮16岁生日派对上的魔术师好
It's better than the magician at my friend Stephanie's 16th birthday
他把我朋友的贞操变没了
that made her virginity disappear.
麦克斯  我们都以你为傲
Max, we're all so proud of you.
明天是你后半生的第一天
Tomorrow is the first day of the rest of your life.
靠  我又得再活一遍啊
Aw, crap. I gotta do this again?
行  但是这次
All right, but this time,
我不要再看励志电影了
I'm not seeing Trouble With the Curve.
你即将要干一番大事业
You are about to do something very big.
对啊  向前迈大步
Yes, she is. Such a big step.
我们一起迈进一大步
Big step for both of us,
因为我也得用我的商业头脑
'cause I'll be using my business acumen
在办公室里工作来帮她赚学费
working in the office to help pay the tuition.
别吵  我是在说麦克斯呢
Shh. I'm talking about Max.
我们大家都凑钱给你买礼物
So we all chipped in to get you something
庆祝你首日上学
for your first day of school.
-也是我的第一天  -卡洛琳  拜托了
- It's my first day too. - Caroline, please,
你害我听不到阿憨说麦克斯什么了
I can't hear Han talking about Max, okay?
给  小宝贝
Here you go, darling,
上学的书包
A book bag for school.
所以给我的惊喜派对是在这之后吗
So what, then? Is my surprise party after this one?
这是怎么一回事
What is happening?
有人笑容满面地对我好
People doing nice things for me and smiling?
是不是又要换寄养家庭了
Am I transferring foster homes again?
里面还有别的东西哦
And there's more stuff inside.
你又把惊喜先剧透出来了
That was supposed to be a surprise too.
惊喜吧
Oh. Surprise!
麦克斯  打开  看看里面东西
Max, open it. Look inside.
对啊  麦克斯  看看里面有啥
Yeah, Max, see what's inside for your big day.
麦克斯的大日子  也是我的大日子哦
Big day for Max. Big day for me as well.
一张交通卡  不是吧
A metrocard? No way.
我送的  无限乘坐哦
From me. Unlimited rides.
无限"骑"[乘坐]吗
Oh. Unlimited rides?
你屁股上的骚货纹身是这个吗
Is that what your tramp stamp says?
本来要跟你吵的  但你这吐槽实在是妙
I was gonna get mad, but that was a damn good one.
这又是啥  阿憨的房子吗
What's this? Han's house?
你简单说句"谢谢"就够了
A simple "thank you" would suffice.
谢谢你送我你的房子  阿憨
Thank you for your house, Han.
铅笔盒  我好喜欢啊
It's a pencil case, and I love it.
我刚才还干坐在这  想着你们会不会
And I was sitting here, thinking how you were
忘了明天也是我的大日子呢
all ignoring my part of the big day.
然后你们就送了我这个
And then, you give me this pencil case
带去上班用的铅笔盒  证明我想错了
to use in the office and prove me wrong.
那是送麦克斯的
That's for Max.
你们他妈脑子是哪有问题啊
What the hell is wrong with you people?
麦克斯都不需要用铅笔
Max doesn't even need pencils.
她会在烘焙东西
She'll be baking.
她是会晕乎乎[烘焙]才对
Well, she'll be baked.
打开看看
Take a look.
大麻烟
Joints.
厄尔  你真是太好了
Earl, that's so sweet.
这一盒够我抽到今天休息时间了
These should last me till recess.
等等  苏菲要送的绣名厨师制服呢
Wait, where's the Chef's coat Sophie had monogrammed?
阿憨  这是我要送的惊喜呢
Han, that was supposed to be a surprise.
我故意的  报应来了吧
Oh, I know. Karma's a bitch.
好吧
Oh, well.
给
Look.
上面有我名字呢
My name's on this.
唯一上面有过我名字的东西
the only thing my name's ever been on before
是验毒尿检杯
is a urine sample.
谢谢你们大家
Thank you, everyone.
所以那书包里没一样东西是给我的吗
So there is nothing in that bag for me?
毛都没有吗
Nothing?
现在如果送我奥列格的鸡鸡热狗  我都愿意收下
I'd even take Oleg's penis in a hot dog bun right now.
马上给你做
I'll be right back.
-要上车啦  -请让让
- Getting on. - Please move.
-上车啦  -让让啊
-姐要上车  -拜托让让
- Getting on. - Please move.
-上啦  -让啊
- On! - Move!
-上  上  -让  让
- On! On! - Move! Move!
我爱死地铁了
I love the subway.
发泄怒气的完美地点
It's the perfect place to get out aggression.
我刚才锤了一拳别人的肚子
I just punched someone in the kidney.
正是在下
It was me.
我知道
I know.
好臭的屁味
Oh, oh, bad smell,
是谁吃了中东蔬菜球啊
Like someone hooked up with a falafel.
-正是在下  -我知道
-It was me. - I know.
-克制点  -抱歉
- Max. - Sorry.
地铁里  飞机上  舞池中  我任屁自放
Subways, planes, and mosh pits, I let it ride.
我爱死这件上衣干洗后清新的味道了
I love the smell of this fresh, dry-cleaned blouse.
我好兴奋我能摆脱那服务生制服
I am so excited to be out of that waitress uniform,
重新穿上我的时尚工装
and back in my chic business clothes,
然后走进我的办公室
and, you know, going to my office,
在那里运用着我的沃顿才华
where I'll probably save the day
拯救办公室於水火之中
using some of my Wharton magic.
我更喜欢你内心希望全灭的样子
You know, I think I like you better without hope.
麦克斯  你知道这学校学费很贵吧
Max, you know this school is expensive, right?
你会抱着积极心态去上课吧
You're going in with a good attitude, right?
不是啊  不然厄尔的"铅笔盒"是干啥用的
No, that's what Earl's pencils are for.
别担心啦  我会尽力
Don't worry, I'll do my best.
你看  这次我有个书包呢
I mean, look, I have a book bag.
以前我去上学  我妈唯一给我带的东西
The only thing my mother ever sent me to school with
就是张写了"帮忙检查虱子"的字条
was a note that said "Check me for lice."
大家送你书包真是太贴心了
It was so sweet of everyone to give you that,
虽然这害我一整晚睡不着
even though I didn't sleep all night about it.
而且看起来不便宜呢
And it looks kind of expensive.
看看是什么牌子的
Check for a designer label.
何必呢  心意最重要嘛
Why? It's the thought that counts.
胡说八道
Since when?
让我看看
Let me see it.
第二大道站
Second avenue station.
这里是第二大道站
This is second avenue.
惨了  麦克斯
No, no, no, Max!
他抢到了书包  很好  麦克斯
No, he got the book bag. Good, Max, good.
千万别放手
Don't let go.
万一车子发动了
What if the train starts to leave
然后我手断了咋办
and my arms pop off?
我还怎么去上烘焙学校啊
How will I go to pastry school?
我就得跟那些残疾用嘴来
I'll be one of those people decorating cookies
装饰饼干的人一样了
with a bag in their mouth.
你是个魔鬼
You are the devil.
魔鬼
The devil.
你就是个渣渣
You have nothing.
拉  麦克斯  快拉  从魔鬼手上拉走
Pull, Max, pull! Pull it from the devil!
拉不走啊  这魔鬼有健身
Can't. The devil works out.
我的书包
My bag.
我的衬衫
My blouse.
我的大麻
My weed.
这下好了  都开始上课了
Oh, great, look. Class has started.
我的新生活已经搞砸了
My new life already blows.
帅气大厨在里面呢
Oh, look. There's Chef gorgeous.
我不想让他看到我这么狼狈
I don't want him to see me like this.
我去洗手间看看
I'm gonna go to the restroom and see
能不能用冷水把这脏污弄掉
if cold water can get out any of the stain.
-快进去上课  -可是我的厨师服跟书包没了
- Go, Max. - But I don't have my chef coat or book bag.
我知道它们只在我生命中存在过几小时
I know I only had them for a couple of hours,
但那是我最美好的时光
but it was the best part of me.
你能行的
You'll do great.
先帮我个忙  检查我有没有虱子
First, do me a favor. Check me for lice.
这门课是设计来向你们介绍
This course is designed to introduce you
一些技术与技巧
to the skills and techniques required
来制作如发面面包
in the production of yeast bread,
酥皮面团  奶黄饼  泡芙
short pastry doughs, custards, pate a choux,
以及蛋糕糊等等
and cake batters.
麦克斯大厨  你迟到了
Chef Max, you are late.
你确定课不是10点17分开始吗
Wait, are sure class doesn't start at 10:17?
对不起  我在地铁上被混蛋给抢劫了
Sorry, I got robbed on the subway by some jerk.
喂喂喂  干嘛指鼻子骂我
Hey, hey, hey, I'm right here.
我没钱走投无路
I ran out of options, and I didn't wanna
又不想跳脱衣舞赚学费  所以...
strip my way through pastry school.
可以靠脱衣舞赚学费吗
That's an option?
好了  厨师们  专心点
All right, Chefs. Let's focus.
他刚是说他想"搞我们"[专心]吗
Did he say he wants to "foke us"?
越洗越糟了
早安啊  碧碧
Morning, Bebe.
天啊  你这是怎么了
Hi. Oh, my God. What happened to you?
我先提醒你  我的医生说
And I should tell you my doctor says
我接下来一个月内都不应该听到坏消息
I'm not allowed to hear bad news for another month.
抱歉我这么狼狈来上班
I apologize for my appearance.
但我们在地铁上被抢了
We got robbed on the subway,
然后被拿着热咖啡的人弄了一身
and then someone hit me with hot coffee.
然后我去用了冷水想洗掉咖啡渍
Then, I went to wash cold water on the stain
结果没洗掉  还弄得像要参加
and somehow wound up entering myself
性感"湿身"选美赛了
in a wet t-shirt contest.
负面能量太多我扛不住
Um, that's a lot of energy for me,
先让我坐在位子上休息
So I'm just gonna need to sit here
然后平静一会吧
for a second and be quiet.
我知道我现在该让你平静  我也支持
I know we're being quiet, which I'm all about,
好可爱的小狗啊
but cute dogs.
谢谢  这是可卡犬
Oh, thanks. They're cocker spaniels.
我拯救了他们
I rescue them.
大家都想着去拯救灰狗  斗牛犬啊
You know, people rescue greyhounds and pit bulls,
但都没人想到可卡也需要拯救
but everyone ignores the cocker spaniel.
都觉得可卡犬恶心  要宰了他们
They're like, "Ew, eye goo. Shoot it."
我养了三只可卡[三根鸡鸡]
I have three cockers.
你有宠物吗
Do you have any pets?
有匹马  叫栗宝
I have a horse, Chestnut.
他是只纯种马
He's a thoroughbred.
我该从哪里开始帮忙呢
Well, what can I do first?
这是什么  为什么给了我果汁菜单
What's this? Why am I holding a juice menu?
每天我们都为所有学生与员工
Every day, we get fresh-pressed juice
买新鲜的鲜榨果汁
for the students and the staff.
太享受了
What a treat.
新鲜果汁是纯骗钱的
Fresh juice is such a scam
但是别人请的就不算
unless someone else is payin'.
我要一杯绿色三号
I'll take the greens number three.
好的  写上单子
Uh-huh, well, put it on the list
然后去问别人要喝什么吧
when you get the other ones.
等等  所以是我得去买果汁吗
Wait, I'm supposed to get the juice?
我就是坏消息集中地
Oh, boy, it's like I'm a bad news machine.
没关系
Okay.
乐意效劳  没意料到  但很乐意帮忙
Happy to do it. Surprised, but happy.
那我可以借一套那可爱的厨师服穿穿吗
Uh, maybe I could change into one of those cute Chef jackets.
尼可拉斯大厨规定了只有烘焙厨师能穿
Oh, Chef Nicholas only permits pastry Chefs to wear these.
但我不能第一天就这么狼狈的出场吧
But I can't meet everyone on my first day looking like this.
当买果汁的人已经够惨了吧
I mean, it's already bad enough I'm the juice girl.
我有一些健身衣服可以给你穿
I have some workout clothes you can wear.
你放心  我一次都还没穿过
Don't worry. I haven't worn them yet.
但总有一天会穿的
But I will someday.
你们好  大家好啊
Hi. Hi, everyone.
我是来问你们喝什么鲜果汁
I'm here to take the fresh juice orders
也顺便说一声  我本来上班穿的不是这个
and also to say this is not what I came to work in.
我穿的衣服可没瞪着大眼的狗头
What I came to work in had less eyes.
卡洛琳  欢迎你
Caroline, welcome.
-在办公室干得怎么样  -很好
- How is it going in the office so far? - So great,
我今天真不是穿这个来上班
and so not what I came to work in.
通常我穿的都是香奈儿  而不是犬衣
I'm usually wearing Chanel, not le chien.
那是法语"狗"的意思
That's "dog" in French.
那也是英语"二"的意思
Oh, 'cause it's "dork" in English.
很高兴见到你们俩
Well, it is lovely to see both of your faces.
同学  我们先从基本的开始
Class, we start with the basics.
不  不  后面的同学
No, no, no, you in the back--
喝果汁吗  小姐  想从一个
Juice, miss? Care for a juice
高考成绩1560分的人那点果汁吗[旧制满分1600]
from someone who scored 1560 on her SATs?
你居然考超过500分
You can score more than 500?
你干嘛要穿这件衣服啊
Why the hell are you wearing that?
这让你的胸部显得更平更悲哀
I didn't think your chest could get any sadder.
这是碧碧的衣服
It's Bebe's.
麦克斯  我来这工作不是帮人点果汁的
Max, taking juice orders is not what I came here to do.
我懂你意思  我点一杯宝石红
I hear you. I'll have the ruby red.
我总是保持花嘴干净[龟头]
I always keep the edge clean,
这样当我挤[射]的时候
So when I'm squeezing it,
奶油[精液]就不会喷得哪儿都是了
It's not gonna have cream popping all over the place.
警世良言啊
Words to live by.
可惜我恰恰相反
I have the opposite problem.
瞧  我的"奶油"喷涌而出
Yo, my cream's poppin' right now.
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?
你答应过我会认真上课的
You told me you were gonna take school seriously.
不能怪我  是那家伙带坏我
It's not me. That guy's a bad influence.
你看他
Look at him.
他长得就像芝麻街卡通里买毒品的人
He looks like someone who sells drugs on Sesame Street.
你敢玩出火就杀了你
You're gonna get in trouble,
我牺牲穿可卡犬衣服
and I am not wearing a cocker spaniel
可不是为了看你被踢出去
so you can get kicked out of class.
好  我知道了
Right. I hear you.
话说我的果汁呢
Now, where's my juice?
麦克斯大厨  快看我的独家技能
Hey, Chef Max. Check out my technique.
超棒超恶心的声音
Awesome gross sound bonus.
大厨  你要觉得这样玩很有意思
Chef, if you find this so funny,
不如你出去跟"五指"姑娘玩吧
why don't you take a fiver?
反正你不就爱说这些吗
Isn't this how your saying goes?
我没爱说这些
I don't have a saying,
但如果我有  那应该是
but if I did, it'd be more like
"口交不算偷吃"
"Eatin' ain't cheatin'."
如果有人觉得有东西很好笑
Anyone else who finds something hilarious
可以跟他一起去走廊
can also go into the hall.
-麦克斯大厨  -不用了  一点都不好笑
- Chef Max? - Nope, nothing 'ilarious.
继续上课吧
Teach on.
不许再开黄腔了
Enough with the dirty jokes.
我们来这的目的是成为优秀的面包师[自慰师]
We are all here to become master bakers.
我在掌握烘焙[自慰]这方面可是下了不少[硬]功夫
Master-baking is something I work really hard at it.
-要成为一名优秀的烘焙师  -我自己去走廊吧
- To be a master baker--  - I'll be in the hall.
-我是迪克  -你刚是说自己是"怪胎"吗
- Hi, I'm Deke. - Did you say "Freak?"
-是迪克  -是"怪咖"吗
- Deke. - Did you say "Geek?"
大"鸟"迪克的迪克
Deke, as in "Big Deke."
我的更大
Mine's bigger.
我们应该成为搭档
We should be lab partners.
来嘛  这组合超棒的
Come on. It'll be bitchin'.
超大号[麦克斯]大鸟  一起做蛋糕
Max and Deke, making cakes.
周日  周日  周日
Sunday, Sunday, Sunday,
主义乐团要为我们带来特别演出
with a special performance by Creed.
好了  别玩了  别玩了
Okay, now stop, stop, stop.
我在努力当个好学生
I am trying to be a good student,
所以你离我远点
so you just stay away from me.
你会带坏我的
You are a bad influence.
我这番话肯定超顺  因为小时候
And I know I nailed that speech 'cause kids at school
同学们总对我说这番话
used to say it to me all the time.
-到时间换卫生棉了吗  -是的
- Time to change your tampon? - Yep.
经期第二天  流量超大
Day two. Serious flow.
腰包真可爱  你的最炫民族风披肩在哪里
Killer fanny pack. Where's your tribal poncho?
那是用来放针的
Ah, keep my needles in this.
你居然还是个瘾君子
You're a drug addict too?
天啊  想不跟你一起混真难
God. You are irresistible.
是用来打胰岛素的  我是个糖尿病患
It's--it's insulin. I'm a diabetic.
一个患有糖尿病的甜点大厨
A diabetic pastry Chef.
你的自毁倾向比我的强多了
Wow, you're even more self-destructive than me.
糖尿病  什么感觉啊
So diabetes, how is that?
很没劲  我宁可得梅毒
Disappointing. I put in for syphilis.
别笑了  老娘要穿着这衣服
Stop laughing. I have to carry 27 juices
去两个街区外扛27杯果汁
2 blocks wearing this.
你干嘛让狗头女这样跟你说话啊
Why'd you let the dog lady talk to you like that?
即使穿着那件傻逼衣服  她还是我的朋友
She's my friend, even in that shirt.
又花了我12块钱
Well, there goes another $12.
我干洗这件衬衫的钱
I have spent more money dry cleaning this blouse
比我健康保险上花的钱还多
than I have on health care.
健保  你是说我们从9毛9店
Health care? You mean that box of band-aids
买回来的那一盒子止血贴吧
We got at the 99 cent store?
我明天一定要漂漂亮亮地去上班
I just have to look good tomorrow.
今天太丢脸了
Today was mortifying.
我被果汁店员叫"倒霉狗"
They called me "sad dog" at the juice place.
"倒霉狗  你的果汁好了"
"Sad dog, your juices are ready."
倒霉狗  上菜了
Sad dog, pick up.
你能拿去十号桌吗  我在照看卡座区
Can you take these to table ten? I'm backed up on the booths.
你去吧  我要坐在这休息一会
Can you? I'm kind of just sitting here a minute,
享受不被人使唤的美好时光
enjoying not being told what to do.
我在那间学校真是受够了
I get enough of it at that school.
听着
Look.
如果你要学人老妈使唤小孩  学像点
If you're gonna do the mother thing, do it right.
把你的手伸进油锅  或更惨一点
Stick your hand in boiling oil or even more painful,
狂看精彩电视台的《日落沙哈》
binge-watch Shahs of Sunset on Bravo.
讲述加州比佛利山的伊朗裔美国人如何
在种族传统和美国现代文化之间寻找平衡的故事
现在就进厨房  我有话跟你说
I need to talk to you in the kitchen now.
出去  有人准备因为培训的事而被训
Leave, someone's about to get schooled about school.
貌似场面会变得丑陋不堪[淫秽下流]
This looks like it's going to get dirty and ugly.
我可以录下来吗
May I film it?
如果可以录  我能放到网上卖吗
And if so, may I then sell it on the internet?
听着  你这么做不能只是为了我
Look. You can't just do this for me.
-说得对  那我们退学吗  -当然不行
- You're right. So we're out? - No, we're not out,
你说过你会为我这么做的
you said you were gonna do this for me.
我知道  可你刚不是说
I know, but you just said
我不能为了你才这么做吗
I can't just do it for you,
我觉得你说得对
And I agree.
-我的意思是  我骗谁啊  -我啊
- I mean, who was I kidding? - Me.
你骗我
You were kidding me.
我去那里上班是想施展我的商业才能
I went in there thinking I was gonna use my business skills,
而我曾经希望跟法国佬
and whatever hope I had of a flirtation
调情卖骚现在也没戏了
with Frenchie McFrench went out the window
因为他看见我穿着那件T恤  上面写着
when he saw me wearing that T-shirt that said,
"记得节育  勿忘阉割"
"Don't forget to spay and neuter me."
好吧  我退学  没关系
Fine, I can quit. It's fine.
-真的吗  -假的  当然有关系啦
- It is? Really? - No, it's not fine.
-我骗谁啊  -我啊  你骗我
- Who am I kidding? - Me. You were kidding me.
你一定要在那里找到
Well, you've gotta figure out something
能让你保持兴趣的东西
there to keep you interested,
因为你去烘焙学校不能只是为了我
because you can't go to pastry school just for me,
而我也不会为了你而退学
and I'm not gonna not go to pastry school for you.
好吧  你说得对  麦克斯
Okay. You're right, Max.
我当然会为你这么做
Of course I'll do it for you.
我只是今天过得很糟糕
I just had a bad day.
我们都是
I mean, we both did.
你丢了书包和大麻
You lost your man's briefcase and your drugs,
而我丢了自尊和可能有的小恋情
and I lost my dignity and a possible love interest.
惊喜吧
Surprise!
瞧  惊喜就应该是这样
See, that's how it's supposed to go.
我们给你买了个新书包
We got you a new book bag.
一套新的大厨制服
Yeah, and a new Chef's jacket.
还有一把弹簧刀
And a switchblade.
对啊  因为我们不想再买第三套大厨服了
Yeah, 'cause we're not buyin' another Chef's jacket.
麦克斯  你知道这意味着什么吗
Max, you know what this means?
我得到两次惊喜礼物  而你毛都没有吗
That I got two surprises, and you got nothing?
不  在学校一切都会好的
No, that everything's gonna work out at that school.
我是说  眨眼之间
I mean, in the blink of an eye,
就像这样  事情可以由坏变好
just like this, things can change from bad to good.
也不算完全变好
Well, not totally good.
我依旧毛都没有
They still haven't gotten me anything.
卡洛琳  有你的礼物
Caroline, you didn't not get anything.
给  你专属的铅笔盒
Here, your very own pencil case.
但没"铅笔"  我的"铅笔"供货商被抓了
But no pencils. My pencil dealer got busted.
谢谢你们  我感动死了
Thank you, guys. I'm touched.
真是万万没想到啊
I was not expecting it.
是吗  你可是拿一哭二闹三上吊来强迫我们
Really? 'cause you kinda bullied us all into it.
我的SAT成绩语言成绩是780分
So that's a 780 on verbal,
数学成绩也是780分
and a 780 on math.
而且我拿的是金融学位
And with my degree in Finance,
在市里跑来跑去买果汁这种事
jackass-ing around the city getting juice
完全是在浪费我的天赋啊
could be seen as a waste of my talents.
我毕业典礼时的优秀学生代表说过
And as the valedictorian at my graduation said--
也就是我自己说过
and I'm stealin' from myself here,
"我看见了金融界的未来
"I've seen the future of Finance,
也就是我们"
and it's us."
所以你是想让我去买果汁吗
So you want me to get the juices?
就今天  拜托了
Just for today. Please?
法式蛋白乾是练习
Meringue cookies are a simple way
裱花袋技巧的最简单的方法
to practice our pastry bag technique.
真是个有趣的技巧啊  大厨
Hm, interesting technique you got going there, Chef.
伙计  我们得抛弃彼此的无聊搭档
Dude, we gotta ditch these deadbeat partners.
我被一位老奶奶拖累
I'm stuck over there with grandma.
不要  我不想换掉我旁边的大胖子
No, I'm staying with the big guy next to me.
他才不会让我惹麻烦
He's not gonna get me in trouble.
他从不说话  快走开
He never talks. Get outta here.
回到你的桌子上去  胖子阿伯特
Go back to your own table, Fat Albert.
《胖子阿伯特》是美国70年代开始风行的热门卡通剧集
主角是一名黑胖子
好吧
Okay.
我回去
I'm going back.
但你叫我胖子阿伯特  是因为我是黑人
And the Fat Albert thing was 'cause I'm black,
不是胖  对不对
Not fat, right?
因为我一年怎么也去两三次健身房吧
'cause I go to the gym two, three times a year.
我听到前面只有说话声  没有干活声
I hear talking, but no baking up front.
不  不  你听到的只有干活声
No, no, no, you only hear baking.
这里在激烈地"干"呢
Just furiously master-baking up here.
蛋白乾要有漂亮的尖角
The meringue needs to have nice peaks.
你们要做出湿湿的尖尖角[乳头]
You are looking to make moist, pointy peaks.
我最喜欢捏"它们"了
I like to pinch them.
主厨  咱俩私下说一句
Chef, seriously, man-to-man,
有个问题
we got a problem.
我觉得麦克斯不应该跟那个大胖子在一组
I don't think Max should be stuck with that big guy.
他太猥琐了
He's not cool.
我刚在那边
I was just over there,
他唯一感兴趣的尖尖角在她身上
and the only pointy peaks he's interested in are hers.
我说的是她的咪咪  主厨
Talkin' boobies here, Chef.
约翰大厨  迪克大厨
Chef John, Chef Deke here
似乎觉得你在性骚扰麦克斯
Seems to think you are sexually harassing Max.
拜托哟
Oh, please.
如果人家要性骚扰别人  那人肯定是你
If I was harassing anyone, it would be you, Chef.
你的魅力无法挡嘛
I mean, come on.
马上回来  姐们儿
Be right back, big Mary.
你真懂我
You know it.
我的果汁呢  都过了一个小时了
Where's my juice? It's been an hour.
情绪波动的精灵去拿了
The mood swing elf's getting them.
听着  我要进去跟尼古拉斯主厨卖骚
Look, I'm coming in there To flirt with Chef Nicholas,
当我进去的时候  我要你说
and when I enter, I need you to say,
"卡洛琳  你看起来美呆了"
"Caroline, you look amazing."
不行
No.
我的身体不允许我说出这种话
I actually physically can't say that.
我宁愿冲进去大喊
I would rather walk in there and yell,
"我有阴虱  刚刚有三只逃跑了"
"I have crabs, and three of them just escaped."
快叫救护车  快叫救护车
Call 9-1-1. Call 9-1-1.
那个可爱的混血男出事啦
Something's happened to the adorable mixed-race one.
迪克
Deke?
他有糖尿病  他需要打胰岛素
He's diabetic. He needs insulin.
这里有人会打针吗
Has anyone here ever administered a needle?
"打针"就跟"把针插进去"的意思一样  对吧
Uh, administer means the same thing as "shove it in," right?
很好  很好  麦克斯  你过来
Good, good, good, Max. Come, come, come.
好的  他的注射器在腰包
Okay, uh, his syringes are in his fanny pack.
老实说  我之前干这种事时
I've actually never done this
都得听着重金属摇滚乐
without Iron Maiden playing in the background,
但我来打打看吧
But I'll give it a shot.
在我性感的身躯上随便打一针就行
Just put it anywhere in my hot bod.
上帝保佑
God help us.
我讨厌针  我不敢看了
Oh, I hate needles. I can't look.
女士们  别惊慌失措好吗
Get it together, ladies.
所以医生不准我抱小孩
This is why I'm not allowed to hold babies.
麦克斯  从现在开始你和迪克一组
Max, I think you and Deke should be lab partners from now on
以防今天的事再次发生
in case something like this happens again.
-没问题吧  -我别无选择
- Is that okay? - I guess if I have to.
麦克斯  你呢
Max?
我也别无选择
I guess if I have to.
你是故意不按时打胰岛素吗
What, did you not take your insulin on purpose?
人家真的很想做你搭档嘛
I really wanted to be your partner.
碧碧  我在这里找不到大厨上衣
Bebe, I can't find a Chef jacket anywhere in here.
很抱歉  我知道我不应该穿那个
And I'm sorry, I know I'm not supposed to wear one,
但我真的很冷
but I'm really cold,
我不能一天都穿着这身衣服走来走去
and I can't walk around like this all day.
或许我可以帮你
Maybe I can help.
你不能又湿又冷地站着
You can't stand there wet and cold.
-穿我的上衣吧  -不  不
- Take my jacket. - Oh, no, no, no.
不用了  那也行
You don't have-- oh, that'll work.
不好意思我里面没穿衣服
I'm sorry about the no shirt under,
我上课的时候  总是觉得很热
but I just get so hot when I'm teaching.
是啊  热  太热[性感]了
Yeah, hot. So hot.
我的天啊[法语]
Oh mon dieu.
我正准备[射]给卡洛琳呢
I was just giving it to Caroline.
我是说  她需要换件衣服
I mean, she needs something to wear,
我就把我的给她了
and--and now, she has it.
大厨  晚点见
Chef, I will see you later.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
麦克斯  我我找到让我性致昂扬的东西了
Max, I think I found something to keep me interested.
这下奇怪了  现在我成了好学生
This is weird. So I'm the good student now?
而你却成了跟老师上床的那个
And you're the one sleeping with the teacher?
我们又没上床
We're not sleeping together.
干嘛这么说  你觉得他想要我吗
Why? Do you think he wants to?
我不知道  但在胖子姐们儿扑过去前
I don't know, but you better hurry it up
你最好早点下手
before big Mary gets him.